IVAN MOLOCHIY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

molochiy.ivan@gmail.com

+380-97-516 25 00

Profile

I have more than 8 years of experience in developing and fixing microservices, web applications, and REST API's and background services using (but not limited to) Golang and Java

Skills

Hard Skills

Soft skills

Strong problem-solving Golang Java ability Team player Spring High emotional intelligence Javascript Flexible SQL NoSQL **Decision Making** Docker Critical thinking Responsible Git Linux, OS X, Windows Social

Self-learner Quick on the uptake

Project Direction

Proven ability to design, develop, fix and unit test a wide variety of projects in different domains

Experience

Edvantis Golang Developer

2017 - 2018

Drilling info

Involved in Natural resources management app development. Fixed and improved authentication and client entitlement services after Red Hat SSO migration

Lohika Java developer

2013-2017

Responsible for development of energy management system. Implemented metrics calculation related to utilities (electricity, gas, water etc.) like regional rollup, usage prediction, budget projection etc. Implemented alerting system and meter data filtering and interpolation Fixed countless issues in background services and web application

Tidemark

Short description: Development and bug fixing of enterprise performance management software Responsibilities: Implemented user task scheduling services. Fixed thread pooling issues Tools: Spring, Spring MVC, Protocol Buffers, JDBCtemplate, Quartz, Jackson, postgresql, Maven, Git, NetBeans

N-IX Java Developer

2011-2013

OpenText

Designed and developed mobile client build management app from scratch. Lead junior members of the team Developed HTTP resolve server for applications requested by client and administration UI application for it. Reverse-engineered and bug fixed legacy application for build management Implemented and optimized fallback HTTP server for proprietary binary protocol

GlobalLogic Java Developer

2010-2011

WDS

Implemented various background services and web application for phone showcase and retail

WeComm

Implemented data providing backend and integrated with user interface built with proprietary software Implemented certificate management portal for mobile client rebranding application

Nice Systems

Developed the extension for video streaming server Fixed threading/socket/JNI video publishing issues, optimized performance of live streaming video publishing, integrated with video encoding software service

Education

Ivan Franko National University of Lviv Master of Applied Mathematics and Informatics

Personal activities

Songwriting	Festivals	Camping
Sound engineering	Gym	Reading
Playing guitar/bass	Gaming	Electronic engineering

Links

GitHub: github.com/iamgoroot
GitLab: gitlab.com/iamgoroot

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/ivan-molochiy